The game is far from over.
Along Came a Spider is a crime, mystery, thriller film directed by Lee Tamahori.
After the harrowing death of his partner, forensic psychologist and best-selling author Alex
Cross cannot forgive himself and has retreated to the peace of retirement.
But when a brilliant criminal kidnaps a senator's young daughter, he is lured back
into action as the kidnapper wants to deal with Alex personally.
Teamed with Jezzie Flanigan, the Secret Service agent assigned to protect the missing girl, Alex follows a serpentine
trail of clues that leads him to a stunning discovery - the kidnapper wants more than just ransom.
Alex Cross, played by Morgan Freeman.
Jezzie Flannigan, played by Monica Potter.
Gary Soneji, played by Michael Wincott.
Ollie McArthur, played by Dylan Baker.
Megan Rose, played by Mika Boorem.
Dimitri Starodubov, played by Anton Yelchin.
Along Came a Spider is a 2001 American thriller film directed by Lee Tamahori.
It is the second installment in the Alex Cross film series and a sequel to
the 1997 film Kiss the Girls, with Morgan Freeman and Jay O.
Sanders reprising their roles as detective Alex Cross and FBI agent Kyle Craig.
The screenplay by Marc Moss was adapted from the 1993 novel by James Patterson.
It received negative reviews on Rotten Tomatoes and mixed reviews on
Metacritic, and it grossed $105.2 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
detective, fbi, teacher, psychologist.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.